Guide to the Reston Reflections oral history collection, 1994-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Transcripts, 1994-2008; (79 boxes)
  - McGrath, Patty, May 24, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - McGrath, Sarah, May 22, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - McGutyre, Pat, May 25, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - McKee, Kathleen Driscoll, June 11, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - McKnight, Maura, April 23, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    518.12
  - McKnight, Maura, January 9, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    505.34
  - McLaughlin and Kulik, April 20, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    516.11
  - McNally, John, May 27, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - McNamara, Michael, June 4, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Mcracken, Joanna, June 9, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    513.23
  - Meader, Marion, December 7, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    453.26
  - Meissner, Irene, May 5, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Melendez, Arturo, 2000s (Box 47, Folder 7)
    516.30
  - Mendelsohn, Stuart, February 23, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    505.35
  - Mendonca, John, June 1, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Mendosa, Julie, June 8, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    513.24
  - Mennard, Millie, May 2, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Mennard, Milly, 2000s (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Mentz, Ed, May 7, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Merriam, Kelly, May 30, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Metz, Joshua, June 2, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Becky, May 10, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Troy, June 1, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Miller, Adina, June 14, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    513.25
  - Miller, Michael, April 12, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    516.16
  - Miller-Qiliras, Melanie, May 7, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Mills, Cindy, May 9, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Mills, Betty, June 2, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Mills, Cindy, May 9, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Minarik, Eileen, June 5, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Minnard, May 31, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    513.26
  - Millon, Tom, June 3, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Mitchell, Flo, June 17, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Mitchell, Flodella, June 2006 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Mobley, Kenneth, June 10, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    513.27
  - Molina, Humberto, May 24, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Moline, Denise, April 3, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    512.3
  - Monroe, Beverley, May 28, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Moody, Margarete, May 16, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Moody, Margarete, May 16, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Mook, Nate, 2000s (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Moore, Barbara, April 9, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    518.8
  - Moore, Christopher, April 1, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    516.2
  - Moore, John E., December 30, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    505.36
  - Morgan, Debbie, December 15, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    453.27
  - Morris, Tom, April 27, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Morris, Jhon, April 14, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    515.32
  - Morse, Caroline, June 6, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Morse, Caroline, June 8, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Moulton, Fred, December 4, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    453.28
  - Muir, Thomas, January 10, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    505.37
  - Munno, Ncole, May 30, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Munroe, Kevin, May 27, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Munroe, Kevin, January 20, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    505.38
  - Murray, John, April 19, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    516.3
  - Murray, Mac, January 10, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    505.39
  - Myers, Marion, June 8, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Myers, Marion, May 9, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Myers, Marion, June 8, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Myrick, Elaine, June 3, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Nagel, Richard, May 21, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Nahorniak, Carol, June 10, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Nahorniak, Carol, June 11, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Nakamura, Bernadette, May 19, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Nandy, Manish, May 10, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Narayan, Mary, May 28, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Narvaez, Ismael, June 1, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Navale, Madhu, May 7, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Nazare, Leni, May 12, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Nebert, Dee, May 12, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Nelson, Barbara, June 13, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Nelson, Barbara, June 14, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Nicoson, Patricia, June 2, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    513.28
  - Nicoson, William, May 31, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    513.29
  - Niemeirer, Myra, May 13, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Niemeier, Paul, May 16, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Nieves, Jim, June 6, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Niggel, Robert, April 12, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    515.21
  - Nims, Chris, June 7, 2008 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Noble, Katherine, June 5, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Noel, Karen, June 5, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Norwood, Jack, April 22, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    518.26
  - Nugent, Joan, December 9, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    453.29
  - O'Connor, Stacy, June 3, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Odlen, Janie, June 2, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - O'Doherty, Lisa, May 8, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - O'Dohaty, Thomas, April 25, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Offholter, Jean, May 1, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - O'Gorman, Boofie, June 3, 2007 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - O'Gorman, Boofie, 2000s (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - O'Gorman, Boofie, May 18, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - O'Gorman, Boffie, June 9, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Oliver, Chris, April 15, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    516.21
  - Olson, Shirley, June 2, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    513.30
  - Olson, Shirley, June 8, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Olson, Shirley and Merritt, May 17, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Olson, Shirley and Merrit, May 17, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Olson, Shirley, June 2006 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Oneil, Greg, January 22, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    505.40
  - O'Rourke, Tom, January 2, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    453.30
  - Oswalt, Belinda, January 21, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    453.31
  - Overton, Ruth, June 5, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Overton, Ruth, June 5, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Pace, Sandi, June 5, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    513.31
  - Packard, Robert, January 3, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    505.41
  - Pagani, Kim, May 3, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Paik, Soon, April 1, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Pajardo, Phyllis, May 9, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Paley-Hume, Lydia, May 7, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Pang, Peter, June 9, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Pappas, James, May 2002 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Pappas, James, June 2, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Park, Steve, January 12, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    505.42
  - Parnicky, Karen, June 8, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    513.32
  - Parnhan, Wendy, May 17, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Passmore, James, June 2, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Pat, May 3, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    515.27
  - Patterson, Ronald, May 14, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Pearson, Robert, May 6, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Pence, Colleen, May 9, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Penland, Laurie, May 19, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Penland, Laurie, May 14, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    518.13
  - Pennino, Martha, January 9, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    506.01
  - Peters, Peggy, May 13, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Peters, Peggy, 2000s (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Peters, Peggy, May 23, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Peters, Peggy, 2000s (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Peterson, Linda, May 27, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Peterson, Cheska, May 22, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Peterson, Natasha, May 9, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Petersen, Lindsey, June 17, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    515.19
  - Petersen, Lindsay, December 26, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    506.02
  - Pew, Joselyn, April 16, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    516.10
  - Philips, Walter, January 12, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    506.03
  - Pinkman, Sue, May 22, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Pinder, Barbara, May 5, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Platt, Leslie, December 26, 2994 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    454.1
  - Plotner, Alan J., May 18, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Plum, Ken, May 17, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Plum, Ken, January 1, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    454.2
  - Plum, Kenneth, march 5, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    506.04
  - Plum, Ken, May 30, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    513.33
  - Plum, Kenneth, June 1, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Plum, Jane, June 9, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Plum, Jane, June 9, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Podell, Laurie, June 4, 2007 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Polivka, Maureen, April 25, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    518.7
  - Ponick, Terence, May 5, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Ponick, Terrence, May 5, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Poppe, Robert, June 4, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    513.34
  - Porter, Donna, June 7, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    513.35
  - Potts, Anne, April 21, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    517.13
  - Potts, Anne and Susan Erdman, 2000s (Box 57, Folder 16)
    454.3
  - Powell, Christopher, June 4, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Powell, Suzi, January 10, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    506.05
  - Price, Charles, May 18, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Principei, Frank, January 2, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    506.06
  - Pronske, Kurt, May 3, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Pronske, Kurt, May 10, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Pronske, Kurt, January 7, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    454.4
  - Pronske, Kurt, January 16, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    506.07
  - Purvance, 2000s (Box 58, Folder 9)
    518.4
  - Pyle, Robert (Mr. and Mrs.), December 19, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    454.5
  - Pyle, Victoria, April 16, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    515.17
  - Quesada, Andres, February 4, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Rabinowitz, Lisa, May 30, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Rabinowitz, Robert, May 16, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Raiston, Chris, June 2, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Ramsey, Nancy, December 11, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    454.6
  - Rando, Guy, June 2, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    514.01
  - Rando, Guy, January 8, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    506.08
  - Rashid, Harunor, May 3, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Ray, Martha, January 10, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    506.09
  - Rector, David, June 7, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    514.02
  - Redick, Julia, April 20, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Regan, Mark, May 30, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Reid, Victoria and Jill Martin, May 29, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    514.03
  - Reiser, Cheri, April 7, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    516.5
  - Renolds, Delores, May 9, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Renshaw, Avis, April 9, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    515.5
  - Rhea, Claude, June 14, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    514.04
  - Rhodes, Elizabeth, June 5, 2007 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Rice-Hughes, Donna, June 9, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Rice, Kim, June 2000 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    514.05
  - Richards, Karen, May 21, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Richardson, Nancy, May 1, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Richardson, Carole, June 23, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Ritchey, Joseph, May 11, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, David, December 29, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    506.10
  - Robinson, David, January 11, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    506.11
  - Robinson, Henry, May 11, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Rodriguez, Anne, May 17, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Roe, Judy, May 17, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Rogers, Martha, December 5, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    454.7
  - Rohrer, David, June 10, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Romero, Gonzalo, May 28, 2008 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Rosily, April 27, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Rosenmund, Joan, May 2006 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Rosenmund, JoAnn, June 12, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Ross, Catherine, May 12, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Roszko, Barbara, May 17, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Rothbart, Linda, June 5, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Rothwell, Delores, May 9, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Rouse, Diana, May 13, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Royal, Diane, May 28, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Rudiselle, Suzanne, June 4, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Rudiselle, Susanne, January 17, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    506.12
  - Ruiselle, Suzanna, May 16, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Rudisille, Susanne, June 4, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Rudorfer, Cynthia, April 17, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    517.10
  - Ruffen, 2000s (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Rust, Thomas Davis (Mayor), January 13, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    506.13
  - Ryan, Helen, May 10, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Ryan, Marshall, 2000s (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Ryan, Nancy, May 31, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Ryan, W. Kevin, May 22, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Rye, Lesile, May 31, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Safi, Sarah, May 5, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Saleem, Omar, June 17, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Saleem, Omar, June 17, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Salin, Dino, January 16, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    506.14
  - Salin, Dino, June 9, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Salin, Dino, June 9, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Salin, Dino, April 30, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Sande, Clay, May 5, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Santos, Brunilda, 2000s (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Santos, Brunilda, June 10, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Sanson, Michelle, April 12, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    518.24
  - Saunders, Mary, May 8, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Saundes, Charles, May 8, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Savage, Ron, January 17, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Sawicki, Carrie, May 30, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Schambach, Pat, January 16, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    506.16
  - Schiffeibein, Patricia, June 7, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Schiffelbein, Patricia, June 7, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Schlosser, John, May 30, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Schmid, John, February 23, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    506.17
  - Schoka, Andy, May 18, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    514.06
  - Scholl, Andrea, May 20, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Schram, Sue, May 4, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Schram, Sue, June 3, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    514.07
  - Schram, Sue, June 7, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Schram, Sue, June 7, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Schram, Sue, December 28, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    454.8
  - Schram, Sue, May 27, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Schreiner, William, June 4, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Schultz, Betsy, December 16, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    454.9
  - Schwartz, Elaine, May 4, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Schwartz, Elaine, 2000s (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Schweitzer, Martha, May 4, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Scira, John, 2000s (Box 64, Folder 8)
    514.08
  - Scott, Janice, June 5, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Scott, Janice and Rodney, May 15, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Scott, Janice, June 5, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Scott, Janice and Rodney, 2000s (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Seager, Joy, June 9, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Seager, Joy, June 9, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Seaton, Pat, June 16, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Seering, Ruby, June 7, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Seering, Ruby, June 7, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Selb, Linda, April 26, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    517.2
  - Sellers, Sharon, May 8, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Shal, Andrey V., May 26, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Sharp, Edward and Beverley, May 16, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Sherman, Gertrude, June 2, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Sherman, Gertrude, May 11, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Sherman, Gertrude, June 10, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Sherman, Gertrude, May 8, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Shepherd, Susan, June 2, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Shepich, Loretta, May 7, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Shinrock, Barbara, April 17, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    517.12
  - Shiner, Josette, May 23, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Shubert, Kay, June 8, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    514.09
  - Shur, Steve, June 8, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Silfin, (Dr.), April 12, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    518.21
  - Silvey, Bedford, May 2, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Silvey, Marilyn, January 17, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    506.18
  - Simms-Smith, Amos, May 11, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Simon, Robert E., June 7, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    514.10
  - Simon, Robert E., April 30, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Simon, Robert E., April 21, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    517.18
  - Simon, Robert E., April 5, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    517.19
  - Simon, Robert E., 2000s (Box 66, Folder 12)
    454.10
  - Simon, Robert E., January 16, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    506.19
  - Simon, Robert, January 21, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    506.20
  - Simpson, Jonathan, June 2, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Simpson, Bette, April 13, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    517.3
  - Singer, Linda, June 10, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Singer, Linda, June 1, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    514.11
  - Singer, Linda, May 2, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Singer, Linda, June 9, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Slack, Connie, December 9, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    454.11
  - Smith, Carol, April 26, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Smith, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Alene, June 9, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Claudia, November 1994 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    454.12
  - Smith, Claudia, April 27, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    517.8
  - Smith, Brian, April 27, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    516.22
  - Smith, Charlie, April 29, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    516.12
  - Smith, Alene, June 9, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Smith-Cohen, Amy, May 15, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Smyers, Robin, June 9, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Smyers, Robin, 2000s (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Smyers, Robin, May 15, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Sneed, Maria, May 9, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Snively, Hoya (Dr.), June 3, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Snowhite, Larry, January 24, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    506.21
  - Sogandares, Frank, June 4, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Spencer, Susan, January 12, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    506.22
  - Spillane, Robert (Dr.), January 15, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    506.23
  - Stanmyre, Charles, December 6, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    454.13
  - Stapleton, Tim, December 18, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    454.14
  - Stevens, Margaret, June 9, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Stewart, Deborah, April 13, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    515.15
  - Stiebel, Miles, April 19, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    517.25
  - Stiebel, Joan, December 31, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    454.15
  - Stine, Mary Kay, January 17, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Stojakovich, Ed, June 3, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Stokes, Eleanor (Dr.), May 2, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Stout, Christine, April 23, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Stout, Shannon, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Stowers, Marcia and Joseph, May 29, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Stowers, Marcia, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Stowers, Joe, May 24, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    514.13
  - Stowers, JOe, 2000s (Box 68, Folder 15)
    454.16
  - Straub, Larry, May 22, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Streiff, Nancy, December 10, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    454.17
  - Stroh, David, May 7, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Suarez, Gloria, June 1, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Suchland, Jack, June 7, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    514.14
  - Susco, Tom, May 21, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Sussman, Gloria, June 5, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Sussman, Glroia, May 8, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Sussman, Gloria, June 5, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Swicord, Beth, April 25, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    517.22
  - Taran, Nadia, June 2000 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    514.15
  - Tate, Norman (Rev.), May 19, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Teatley, Oliver, May 2, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Tetlyfio, Geoffry (Dr.), May 22, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    518.11
  - Tenenhouse, Eva, May 10 and 13, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Tenenhouse, Eva, May 13, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Terio, Cheryl, June 13, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Terry-Todd, Terlene, April 24, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Terry-Todd, Terlene, February 16, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    506.28
  - Thayer, Joan P., January 17, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    506.25
  - Thillmann, John, May 24, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    514.16
  - Thoesan, Richard, January 6, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    506.26
  - Thomas, Michael, May 30, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Thomas, Howard and Margaret, June 7, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    514.17
  - Thomas, Odessa, June 6, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Jeffrey, May 26, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Thompson-Deahl, Claudia, January 13, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    504.35
  - Thompson-Diehl, Claudia, May 22, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Thompson, Claudia, June 9, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Thompson, Kay, June 1, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Thoreson, Holly, April 19, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    515.26
  - Thrall, Gloria, June 8, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Thrall, Gloria, June 15, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Tierney, Leslie, June 8, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    514.18
  - Toatley, Olivia, May 2, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Toatley, Olivia, May 6, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Toatley, Olivia, June 5, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    514.19
  - Tobey, Phil, January 20, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    506.27
  - Tobey, Phillip, April 21, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    518.6
  - Tomaino, May 28, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Toohey, Sarah, 2000s (Box 71, Folder 7)
    514.20
  - Totten, Rebecca, May 28, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Tran, Tuyen, June 3, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Trickett, Joyce and Bessie, December 11, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    454.18
  - Tsi, Mary Ann, May 24, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    514.21
  - Turner, Chris, April 30, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    518.16
  - Twohie, George, May 10, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Uhrig, Rick, June 7, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Ungerer, Susan, June 6, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Ungerer, Susan, June 6, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Ungerer, Susan, May 11, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Updike, Ruth, December 30, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    506.29
  - Urban, Philip, June 5, 2008 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Valenti, John (Dr.), May 19, 2008 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Valbusa, Silvio, April 21, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    512.7
  - Van Lane, Sheila, June 4, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Vanemden, Julie, 2000s (Box 72, Folder 7)
    454.19
  - Van-Vlit, Audrey, May 4, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Vaughn, Ellen, June 9, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Veatch, Chuck, June 4, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    514.22
  - Veatch, Charles, June 3, 2008 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Veatch, Charles, May 9, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Veatch, Charles, April 5, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    516.7
  - Vest, Bobby (Mrs.), November 27, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    454.20
  - Via, Kim, May 9, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Viledomine, Joseph, May 2, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    517.7
  - Vincent, Marie, June 5, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    514.23
  - Viray, Tina, 2000s (Box 73, Folder 4)
    514.24
  - Vivona, Catherine, January 5, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    506.30
  - Vliet, Van (Mrs.), December 21, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    454.21
  - Volloy, Jerry, May 20, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Vongsarat, Ketsana, May 9, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Wacker, Winslow, June 9, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Wacker, Winslow, June 9, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Waldrop, Jane, May 18, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Walker, Robert, May 7, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Walker, Elfriede, April 30, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Wallenstein, Sheri, June 3, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Waleoff, Carol, January 15, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    506.31
  - Walnetski, Carol, April 23, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    516.15
  - Walsh, Barry, May 24, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Walsh, David and Allison Grader, May 6, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Walsh, LIsa (Dr.), May 19, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Ward, Lawrence, June 4, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Watt, Dan L., April 5, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    516.6
  - Weatherwax, Holly, May 5, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Wehmerhanlon, Harriet, 2006 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Weinhera, Fred, January 9, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    506.32
  - Weinstein, Rosa, January 12, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    506.33
  - Wellborn, Anne, June 2, 2006 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Welsh, Carol, May 23, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Welsh, Carol, June 5, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 12)